indiacarnews.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - | India Car News

##### Privacy Policy

IndiaCarNews.com (“Website”) values its readers and ensures to protect privacy of personal information of our readers. If in case we use personal information of our readers we make sure it has been done in a protected manner and readers are notified proactively.

The answers to all the questions, as to the intensity of personal information collected from the readers, how and where it would be utilized are explained in the Privacy Policy. Privacy Policy could be referred to as a legal document, it also explicates the steps that are taken by the website to maintain security of readers’ personal information and place where it will be used. The legal document also explains the procedure to either correct or omit information from our database which can be done at any given time by the readers.

You can further inquire about the above given statement and clear your doubts by mailing us at contact@indiacarnews.com

**Here is the complete policy, please read carefully:**

At India Car News we believe in keeping any sort of personally identifiable information like name, address and telephone number shared on our website confidential. We assure our readers that we follow all necessary measures required to safeguard privacy of our readers on India Car News.

It is not mandatory to reveal your personal information and identity for visiting out website. However, we keep an account of the internet addresses of the realms from where our readers can be redirected to us. The collected data is scrutinized minutely in order for us to know interests or our visitors.

Cookies are used on some of the pages on our websites that help us to have a better understanding of the visitors’ experience. These cookies are sent to the browser of the visitor by our website for them to have a better experience on their next visit. Visitors have the liberty to accept or deny the cookie by setting their browser to remind them when a cookie is sent.

We can use personal information of the visitors like name, physical address or telephone number, email address, mobile number only if they have volunteered to share it with us.

Visitors/readers will be informed proactively whenever their personal information is being taken and we vouch to use it for that specific reason.

Though it depends on the visitor/reader to decide whether they want to share their personal information with us or not. Even if visitors do not intend to share their personal information required by us for certain divisions they will still be allowed to visit our website but they might not be able to have access to specific options and services.

India Car News will make sure to shield information provided by the visitors to us. Through our special security tools we ensure to protect privacy of information of our readers and unable unauthorized access or acknowledgment.

Without consent of our visitors, India Car News will never share or reveal any information pulled from the registration for use of any other online service. The information can be used by us for our readers to have an enhanced experience on our website or for betterment of the website. India Car News can also use the information to contact our readers.

By agreeing to continue using India Car News or by not withdrawing your registration on our site implies that you have thoroughly read and understood our terms and are ready to comply with our privacy policy.

In case of any modification or change in the privacy policy we will update it on our website and readers are requested to stay updated on that.

We would like bring to our readers’ notice that India Car News under any situation will not be accountable for any loss, damage etc caused to visitors.

Under the Information Technology Act, 2000 and the reformed clauses related to electronic records in numerous statutes as modified by the Information Technology Act, 2000, this document is as good as an electronic record. This is a system generated electronic record which does not need any physical or digital signatures.

For getting a knowhow of your interest, advertising cookies will be placed on your system during the course of browsing through our website. The personal information of the readers can also be used for the sole reason of rendering an improved service to our visitors.
